"problem": "No such column 'Subject_Specialization__c' on entity 'Account'. If you are attempting to use a custom field, be sure to append the '__c' after the custom field name. Please reference your WSDL or the describe call for the appropriate names.",
"problem": "Variable does not exist: Subject_Specialization__c",
"problem": "No such column 'Is_Active__c' on entity 'Account'. If you are attempting to use a custom field, be sure to append the '__c' after the custom field name. Please reference your WSDL or the describe call for the appropriate names.",
"problem": "No such column 'Is_Completed__c' on entity 'Period__c'. If you are attempting to use a custom field, be sure to append the '__c' after the custom field name. Please reference your WSDL or the describe call for the appropriate names.",
"problem": "Variable does not exist: Is_Completed__c",
"problem": "Variable does not exist: Topic_Discussed__c",
"problem": "Variable does not exist: Completion_Time__c",
"problem": "Field does not exist: Topic_Discussed__c on Period__c",
"problem": "Field does not exist: Is_Completed__c on Period__c",
"problem": "Field does not exist: Completion_Time__c on Period__c",
"problem": "Unable to find Apex action class referenced as 'MarksheetController'.\nUnable to find Apex action class referenced as 'MarksheetController'.",
"problem": "Unable to find Apex action class referenced as 'MarksheetController'.\nUnable to find Apex action class referenced as 'MarksheetController'.",
